<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Portfolio | Donaldson Measurement Group</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Our Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:4321/media/icon_hu11734318148517933569.png</url>
      <title>Our Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Foundry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/good-foundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/good-foundry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Donaldson Measurement Group, we are pioneering research in economic security and well-being. In partnership with The Good Foundry, our team is developing and validating a multidimensional scale that extends the PERMA+4 framework to include critical economic stability factors such as income consistency, job security, and financial resilience. Leveraging rigorous literature reviews, international survey data, and advanced statistical analyses in R, our research delivers actionable insights that enhance both personal and workplace outcomes. Our innovative approach bridges cutting-edge psychometrics with applied positive psychology, empowering organizations to cultivate healthier, more resilient communities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PERMA&#43;4 Collaborative</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/perma4_collaborative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/perma4_collaborative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Led by Dr. Stewart I. Donaldson and Dr. Scott I. Donaldson, the PERMA+4 Collaborative offers innovative measurement scales and practical tools to assess and nurture the nine building blocks of well-being and positive functioning. Building on Professor Martin Seligman’s original PERMA model, PERMA+4 expands the framework to include additional dimensions that predict optimal performance at work, school, and in life. Our global community of researchers and practitioners shares resources, validated scales, and peer-reviewed scientific findings to promote well-being and vitality worldwide. Explore our site for definitions, validated tools, and key publications—or email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Stewart.Donaldson@cgu.edu&#34;&gt;Stewart.Donaldson@cgu.edu&lt;/a&gt; to join the initiative free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle McQuaid Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/mcquaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/mcquaid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with Michelle McQuaid’s group, we have engaged in a multi-year partnership with the University of Melbourne Centre for Wellbeing Science to advance the science of well-being. Our joint efforts have extended across multiple organizations, driving initiatives to enhance well-being in diverse settings. Through our work, we have published several peer-reviewed papers on PERMA+4 measurement, employing advanced methodologies such as item response theory and a systems-informed approach. Our research not only deepens the understanding of well-being dimensions but also provides practical tools for organizations committed to fostering thriving, resilient communities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
