<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Portfolio | Donaldson Measurement Group</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Our Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:4321/media/icon_hu11734318148517933569.png</url>
      <title>Our Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle McQuaid Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/mcquaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/mcquaid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further event details, including page elements such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PERMA&#43;4 Collaborative</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/perma4_collaborative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/perma4_collaborative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Led by Dr. Stewart I. Donaldson and Dr. Scott I. Donaldson, the PERMA+4 Collaborative offers innovative measurement scales and practical tools to assess and nurture the nine building blocks of well-being and positive functioning. Building on Professor Martin Seligman’s original PERMA model, PERMA+4 expands the framework to include additional dimensions that predict optimal performance at work, school, and in life. Our global community of researchers and practitioners shares resources, validated scales, and peer-reviewed scientific findings to promote well-being and vitality worldwide. Explore our site for definitions, validated tools, and key publications—or email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Stewart.Donaldson@cgu.edu&#34;&gt;Stewart.Donaldson@cgu.edu&lt;/a&gt; to join the initiative free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Foundry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/projects/good-foundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/projects/good-foundry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Donaldson Measurement Group, we are pioneering research in economic security and well-being. In partnership with The Good Foundry, our team is developing and validating a multidimensional scale that extends the PERMA+4 framework to include critical economic stability factors such as income consistency, job security, and financial resilience. Leveraging rigorous literature reviews, international survey data, and advanced statistical analyses in R, our research delivers actionable insights that enhance both personal and workplace outcomes. Our innovative approach bridges cutting-edge psychometrics with applied positive psychology, empowering organizations to cultivate healthier, more resilient communities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
